<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>3d Printer on </title>
    <link>/tags/3d-printer/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 3d Printer on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 13:56:47 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/3d-printer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Week 4</title>
      <link>/posts/week4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 13:56:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/week4/</guid>
      <description>With our nice four day week, I continued to design the intricate systems on the float, with the main focus on the Battery Holder. This brick of plastic is designed to hold 8 AA batteries. Last year we used off the shelf battery holders, which were nice and easy, especially since we were in a time crunch, however they were not very space effecient. This year we are going a different route.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 3</title>
      <link>/posts/week3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 13:37:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/week3/</guid>
      <description>This week I fully focused on the float, and particulary the anti rotation rods. I have been trying to figue out what material to use for them fou a couple weeks now, but this is the first week where I have made it a goal, and not an overarching requirement. This is much easier said than done. Last week we diecided that it wasn&amp;rsquo;t worth the time and effort to use piping to hide the wires, which is a bit sad, but also makes my life so much easier.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 1</title>
      <link>/posts/week1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 11:39:42 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/week1/</guid>
      <description>This past week has been rough as it&amp;rsquo;s our first almost full week back in shop and it is fairly hot with super high humidity to go along with it. In the shop I have been primarily working on the fish feeder for the biotech shop here in the voc. I have also been working on this website which has been pretty frustrating and rewarding.
The fish feeder was originally built by students before my time, and its main purpose is to feed the fish that the biotech shop has automatically.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
